Yes, so when we look at the 12-month potential return, there is
a stock of AE which features a
potential return of 22, as told by End
Street analysts, and a price target of 850 has been
given. This is the overall consensus analyst
expectations. The first
reason is that the valuations of AE are quite
cheap. AE trades at 0.6 times price to EV.
And if seen in the overall context, among
all the listed
life insurance companies, LIC has the cheapest
valuations on this valuation metric. When we
talk about overall EV,
a good growth has started to be seen in EV as well, so that is a
positive thing. The management is quite focused.
Now the real thing is
how to optimize the new agency force and
how to increase its efficiency. The
management has also made a plan to strengthen the Banka channel,
so going forward, that will also be a
positive unlock. Going forward,
LIC's focus is more on non-par, which is
better margin.  If it gives versus par
products, then a flip can come on that too,
so if you look at the overall commentary and assess it, then the
overall market
and
analysts are bullish on LIC. The demand for fuel in India and across the world is
at a record level and in such a situation, oil
marketing companies are getting a lot of profit.